Chiba?
Чиба?
怎麼了嗎？
что происходит?
我的褲子不給我穿了。
Мои штаны больше не доступны.
什麼鬼？
Что за хрень?
我的褲子不見了。
Мои штаны исчезли.
我聽不懂
я не понимаю
請幫我找褲子。
пожалуйста, помоги мне найти их.
但你的褲子就在身上，白痴嗎？
но на тебе же есть штаны. ты идиот?
我他媽是水果公主。
Я чертова принцесса фруктов.
為何？
зачем?
所以，可以幫我找褲子嗎？
так, ты поможешь мне найти мои штаны?
為何...
зачем...
為何？我的褲子有危險了。
зачем? мои штаны в опасности.
唉，希望你哪天可以回復正常。
Надеюсь, ты когда-нибудь будешь нормальным.
現在我，都沒在想什麼
I've got nothing on my mind at all
為何，為何？
What for, what for?
除了你，都沒在想什麼
I've got no one on my mind but you
大概又在邊想邊說
guess I'm thinking out loud
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
你是我世上最好的朋友
You're my best friend in the world
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
我想吃披薩，沒錯。
I want pizza, for sure.
我們聊天有夠蠢
We say the dumbest shit
不會有其他成份
wouldn't have it any way
半夜
Late nights
或著凌晨
early mornings
早五點，來講幹話
5am, time for shitposts
哇幹—
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
我又忘了要去睡
I forgot to sleep again
希望我早上眼睛不會痛死
Hope my eyes don't hurt like hell in Morning
噢。
Oh.
一定
They will
一定痛到要死
They'll hurt in the morning
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
你是我世上最好的朋友
You're my best friend in the world
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
我想吃披薩，沒錯。
I want pizza, for sure.
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
你是我世上最好的朋友
You're my best friend in the world
為何，為何
What for what for
為何？
What for?
我想吃披薩，沒錯。
I want pizza, for sure.